Adventures in Babysitting is a comedy, family,
adventure film directed by John Schultz.
Two teen rival babysitters, Jenny and Lola, team up to hunt down one of their kids
who accidentally ran away into the big city without any supervision.
Jenny Parker, played by Sabrina Carpenter.
Lola Perez, played by Sofia Carson.
Emily Cooper, played by Nikki Hahn.
Katy Cooper, played by Mallory James Mahoney.
Trey Anderson, played by Max Gecowets.
Bobby Anderson, played by Jet Jurgensmeyer.
Adventures in Babysitting is a 2016 American adventure comedy television film
directed by John Schultz and starring Sabrina Carpenter and Sofia Carson.
It is a remake of the 1987 film of the same name.
The film premiered on Disney Channel in the United States and Canada on June
24, 2016, and is the 100th Disney Channel Original Movie.
The tone is lighthearted.